《指定幸存者》前情提要
Previously on "Designated Survivor"...
枪
Gun!
不
No!
有几块子弹碎片残留在你的胸腔里
Several bullet fragments lodged in your chest.
我们需要尽快动手术
We need to operate as soon as possible.
先生  你现在是美国代理总统了
Sir, you're now the acting president of the United States.
找到枪手了  他们在指挥中心等你
They found the shooter. They're waiting for you at Command Ops.
柯克曼总统会想要生擒他的
President Kirkman would have wanted to take him alive.
这样不对  下达命令吧  就地射杀
That's a mistake. Give the order. Shoot to kill.
处决疑犯
Execute.
目标已歼灭
Target neutralized.
亚特伍德先生  只要你照我说的去做
Mr. Atwood, your son will be safe
你的儿子就会没事的
as long as you do - everything I tell you to do.
汉娜·威尔士  他们抓到的是她吗
Hannah Wells? That's who they have in custody?
弄清楚她到底知道什么
Find out what she knows.
如果总统想要答案
And if the President wants answers,
我只会告诉一个人
I'll give them to one person --
总统本人
the President himself.
所有人都出去
Clear the floor!
我知道你想告诉我一些
I understand you have some things
关于彼得·麦克利什的事情
you want to tell me about Peter MacLeish.
是的  总统先生
Yes, sir. I do.
麦克利什当时藏在防爆掩体里面
MacLeish was hiding in a bomb shelter?
在爆炸之前就藏进去了
Moments before the explosion,
在播放途中有一个34秒的间隙
there was a 34-second gap in the broadcast feed.
他准确地知道何时该离开
He knew exactly when to leave his seat.
他从最开始就牵涉此事
He was involved from the very beginning.
禽兽
What a monster.
开枪射击他的人  麦克利什也认识他吗
The man who shot him -- MacLeish knew him?
是的  他们一起在阿富汗服过役
Yes. They served together in Afghanistan.
前中情局特工内斯特·洛萨诺
Former CIA operative Nestor Lozano,
代号"卡特兰"
code name "Catalan."
中央情报报告
内斯特·罗萨诺  化名卡特兰
总统先生  我现在没有所有证据
Sir, I don't have all the pieces,
但在麦克利什议员当选副总统之前
but I did feel I had enough to go
我觉得自己证据足够去告诉霍斯拉滕议员了
to Speaker Hookstraten before MacLeish was confirmed.
没错  你这么做了
Damn right you did.
那时发生了什么事
What exactly happened there?
在去听证会的路上  我遇到了袭击
I was attacked on the way to the hearing.
我在去楼雷本大厦
I was on my way to meet Speaker Hookstraten
见霍斯拉滕议员的路上遇袭
at the Rayburn Building.
某人撞了我车的中部  想将我掐死
Someone T-boned my car, tried to strangle me.
我逃走了  但他拿走了我的文件
I got away, but he took my file.
幸运的是  里特特工能够
Luckily, Agent Ritter was able to secure
安全地从局里拿到另一份副本
another copy from the agency.
我真蠢
I feel so stupid.
麦克利什愚弄了所有人  总统先生
MacLeish fooled everyone, sir.
除了她  她看透了他
Not her. She saw right through him.
副总统先生
Mr. Vice President.
-赛斯  我以为你在医院呢  -刚回来
- Seth, I thought you'd be at the hospital. - Just got back.
他怎么样  恢复得快吗
How is he? Recovering rapidly.
总统应该在这周结束之前
The President should be back in the residence
-回到白宫  -好消息
- by the end of the week. - Great news.
说到消息  我们注意到...
Speaking of news, sir, we noticed your team --
你的团队今天晚些时候安排了一场新闻发布会
uh, that your team scheduled a press conference for later today.
我认为需要使公众安心
Yeah, I-I think the people need reassurance
美国仍然在
that their country remains in capable hands
柯特曼总统的统领之下
with President Kirkman in charge.
您的情操真是让人钦佩
It's an admirable sentiment.
只是  我对这个时机很好奇
Just, uh, curious about the timing.
也许您能让我们看看您的发言
Perhaps we could take a look at your remarks.
都搞定了  谢谢  赛斯  谢谢你
It's handled. Thank you, Seth. Thank you.
所以  麦克利什在与艾尔萨卡合作
So, MacLeish was working with Al-Sakar.
艾尔萨卡不是爆炸事件的罪魁祸首
Al-Sakar isn't behind the bombing.
你说什么
I beg your pardon?
当我在审问马吉德·纳萨尔时
When I interviewed Majid Nassar,
他说他之所以承认负责此次袭击事件
he told me that he took responsibility for the attack
就是为了让真正的凶手脱离我们的视线
in order to divert us from the real conspirators.
如果不是艾尔萨卡的话
Well, if it wasn't Al-Sakar --
麦克利什也不可能一个人完成这件事
I mean, MacLeish couldn't have done this on his own.
-谁是他的同伙  -我们还不知道
- Who is he working with? - We don't know yet.
查尔斯·兰登脱不了关系
Charles Langdon is involved.
里士满总统的幕僚长
President Richmond's Chief of Staff?
我以为他在爆炸中牺牲了
I thought he died in the bombing.
我可以亲自作证  他在爆炸中存活
I can personally verify that he survived the explosion.
我曾亲眼见过他
I saw him myself.
事实上  他正藏匿在某个...
In fact, he's hiding out in some --
不好意思
I'm sorry.
威尔士探员  这是我妻子  艾丽克斯
Agent Wells, this is my wife, Alex.
-很高兴见到你  -夫人您好
- Pleased to meet you. - Ma'am.
请继续
Please continue.
请恕我直言  总统先生  此消息
Respectfully, sir, this information
只能向您和您的安保团队透露
is only for you and your security team.
威尔士探员  我向你保证
Agent Wells, I promise you --
不用  没关系的  汤姆
No, no, it's okay, Tom.
我过会儿再来
I'll -- I'll come back.
我可以向你保证  没有这个必要
I assure you that wasn't necessary.
-麦克  请  -对不起  总统先生
- Mike, please -- - I'm sorry, Mr. President,
但我不得不赞同威尔士探员的做法
but I have to agree with Agent Wells.
第一夫人不在您的安保团队内
The First Lady isn't a part of your security team.
她没有保密权限
She doesn't have code-word clearance.
她对这个威胁评估是知情的
She knows about the threat assessment --
那就是个错误  总统先生
And that was a mistake, sir.
你当时可没这么说
You didn't say that at the time.
我现在说了
I'm saying it now.
总统先生  我们现在面临的是一起
Mr. President, we're dealing with a conspiracy
极其危险叵测的阴谋
that's so deep, so dangerous
以至于没有人是安全的
that nobody's safe.
同时  向外部人员透露信息
And not only is sharing information
不仅仅会对国家安全造成威胁
with outside personnel a threat to national security.
而且也会使您信任的人处于危险之中
It also puts the people you confide in at risk.
先生  您必须缩小亲信的范围
Sir, you need to tighten your circle.
那好吧
Okay.
我们现在该做什么
What do we do now?
我想让麦克利什尽快落网
I want MacLeish in custody as soon as possible.
通常来说  我会建议咨询总检察长
Ordinarily, I'd say we consult with the Attorney General.
但是我们现在没有总检察长
But we don't have an Attorney General.
我知道我们可以相信谁  我能联系他吗
I know someone we can trust. Can I reach out to him?
可以
Okay, good.
我可以给你提供一间办公室
I've got an office you could use.
让你从秘密通道自由进出
We can get you in and out through covert access
同时维持对外你仍处于拘留之中的说辞
and maintain your cover story you're still in police custody.
-你得秘密行动  -好的
- You need to stay in the shadows. - Okay.
我需要你再回来时
I want you to come back to me
给我一个捉拿麦克利什的计划
with a plan on how to get MacLeish.
那个混蛋会付出代价的
The son of a bitch is gonna pay.
指定幸存者
第一季 第十二集
你就不能阻止他吗
You can't stop him?
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
副总统有权利
The vice president has the authority
安排他自己的新闻发布会
to schedule his own press conferences.
麦克利什的新闻发布会是怎么回事
Hey, what's this about a MacLeish press conference?
翻译     Margaery  Silence  爱MQ的尼基塔
副总统有权安排自己的
The vice president has the authority to schedule
-新闻发  -这我理解  但为什么是现在
- his own press -- - I understand that, but why now?
这问题你得问麦克利什
You'd have to take that up with MacLeish.
翻译     Lynn_宁  kiki考试加油  长颈鹿
我也想
Well, I'd like to,
但总统给我交待了行动项目清单
but I have a laundry list of action items from POTUS.
-你什么时候跟他说过话的  -一小时前吧
- When did you speak to him? - About an hour ago.
翻译     Michael  星星与野狗  子V  胡说大王
他没告诉我你为什么要调查
And, no, he didn't say why you were looking into
我两年半前打的电话
the phone calls I made 2 1/2 years ago.
老实说  我觉得现在不适合问这个问题
And, frankly, I didn't think it was the right time to ask.
翻译     Sienna  pang  薇薇安  斗斗
有情况及时通知我  好吗
Keep me posted, all right?
有什么是我不知道的吗
Am I missing something here?
校对     星星与野狗  长颈鹿
有人要说吗
Anyone?
时间轴     姜姜  Avis  壬虚浪影
为什么是我
Why me?
因为你是前检察官
Because you're a former U.S. Attorney.
你具备刚正不阿的品格
You're a man of absolute integrity.
而如今  总统需要一个
And right now, the president needs
后期     虫虫不咬人
无可指责的法律顾问
a legal advisor who's above reproach.
你说的有些超出我的职责范围了
What you're asking is just a little above my pay grade.
总监     MQ小早
这超过了所有人的职责范围
Well, it's above all of our pay grades.
这件事是史无前例的
What we're talking about is completely unprecedented.
但总统需要顾问
But the president needs counsel,
我已经告诉他我们可以指望你
and I might have already told him that we can count on you.
那么  可以吗
So...can we?
你这么一番甜言蜜语  我怎么能拒绝
Well, when you sweet-talk a guy like that, how can I refuse?
在过去的几周里
Through these past weeks,
柯克曼总统证明了他是我们可以信赖的领导人
President Kirkman has shown himself to be a leader we can trust,
具有良好品德和能力
a leader who has the virtue and strength
使国家团结一致  我对他的归来
to keep this nation united, and I couldn't be more thrilled
表示兴奋不已
to be welcoming him back to the helm.
刺杀总统未遂与国会爆炸案
The assassination attempt and the Capitol bombing
是针对我们民主共和国
were attacks on the very foundations
根基的攻击  但他们都失败了...
of this democratic republic, and they failed...
-你知道这件事吗  -他们也永远不会成功
- Did you know about this? - ...just as they will always fail...
-赛斯提醒过我  -...一次又一次
- Seth gave me a heads-up. - ...time and time again...
他可真是有胆量啊
Wow. He's got some nerve going out
-就这么独自上阵  -不仅因为我们强大
- on his own like that. - ...not only because we're strong,
还因为我们团结一心
but because we are united,
秉持着共同价值观与希望
woven together through common values and hope.
在此  我想感谢勇敢的执法部门官员
I'd like to thank the brave law-enforcement officers
将...
who brought the --
我得回白宫了
I need to go back to the White House.
你很快就能出院了
Yeah, well, you'll be out of here soon enough.
不  我是说现在  我不能在这干坐着
No. I mean now. I can't just sit here.
汤姆  你刚受到枪击  能活下来已是万幸
Tom, you just got shot. You are lucky to be alive.
艾丽克斯  这一切的幕后主使依然逍遥法外
Alex, the people that are behind this are still out there.
白宫里出了个叛徒
There's a traitor in the White House.
我干等在这里是抓不到他们的
I am not gonna find them by just sitting here.
好吧  汤姆  我得跟你说件事
O-Okay, Tom, I need to tell you something.
什么
What?
在你中枪前不久
Minutes before you got shot,
艾米丽发现是当初
Emily found out that it was Aaron
是亚伦打电话给五角大楼的
who made that call to the Pentagon.
什么
What?
艾米丽为什么要告诉你这种事
Why the hell is Emily talking to you about stuff like this?
她为什么不来找我
Why didn't she come to me?
这是我们第一次有机会谈这事
This is the first opportunity that we've had.
至于亚伦
And with regards to Aaron,
肯定是有什么解释的
there has to be some kind of explanation.
任何人
I mean, any number of people
都有可能让他打这通电话
could have asked him to make that call.
嗯  但我们得考虑的确是他的可能性
Okay, but we have to consider the possibility that it is him.
好  那我会跟他谈  用证据跟他对质
Fine, then I'll talk to him, confront him with the evidence,
-他能自我辩驳  -不行
- and he can explain himself. - You can't.
汤姆  你自己之前都说
Tom, you yourself said just the other day
我们不能相信任何人
we can't trust anyone.
我看着艾伦奋死拼搏
I watched Aaron fight tooth and nail
来保卫和守护我的总统之位
to protect and secure my presidency.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
如果艾伦与恐怖分子有关  如果
If Aaron is involved with the terrorist -- if --
你面对他  对他摊牌
and you confront him and you show him your hand,
你是把自己推向更危险的境地中
you're putting yourself at even more risk.
并不是我在查清楚之前
Well, it's not exactly like I can freeze him out
能把他排除在外  我需要他的帮助
until I get to the bottom of this. I need his help.
一定有办法能在不引起怀疑的情况下
But there has to be a way to keep him at arm's length
疏远他的办法
without arousing suspicion.
这太不可思议了
This is unbelievable.
我是说  动用的资源和企划
I mean, the resources involved and the planning...
一场副总统参与的阴谋
a conspiracy that reaches all the way to the vice president.
我很抱歉我怀疑你了
I'm sorry I doubted you.
不仅仅是局里
It's not just the bureau.
整个国家都亏欠了你许多
The whole country owes you a great debt.
谢谢  长官
Thank you, sir.
不幸的是  这些证据还不够充足
Unfortunately, this isn't enough.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
知道麦克利什有罪是一回事
It's one thing to know that MacLeish is guilty.
定罪是另一回事
It's another one to nail him for it.
我们还需要什么  我有照片  我有
What more do we need? I have the photos. I have the...
你说的可是指控美国的副总统
You're talking about accusing the vice president of the United States
参与了史上最严重的犯罪之一
of being involved in one of the greatest crimes in history.
我们需要能将他和阴谋联系起来的直接证据
We need direct evidence tying him to the conspiracy.
我们甚至都没有足够的证据拘留他
We don't even have enough to detain him,
更别说让他害怕了
much less make him sweat.
那么我们去找实证  找人对他
Then we find grounds. We -- We get someone
施施压力  逼他坦白
to -- to apply the heat, and we flush him out.
找谁
Who?
枪手是我们最大的希望
The gunman was our best bet.
但他死了
He's dead.
麦克利什有其他的同伙
MacLeish has other partners.
对  我以为你说你没有关于她的线索
Right. I thought you said you didn't have a lead on her.
我是没有  但是杰森·亚特伍德也许有
I don't. But Jason Atwood might.
杰森
Jason.
汉娜
Hannah.
让我们单独说说话  谢谢
Leave us now. Thank you.
我让他们把监控关了
I had them turned off.
没有耳目  只有你我
No eyes, no ears, just you and me.
见到你真好
It's good to see you.
你还好吗  发生了什么
How -- How are you? What happened to you?
没什么  我还好
It's nothing. I'm okay.
你如何
How are you?
我的家人怎么样了  卢克怎么样
How's my family? How's Luke?
-没人跟你说吗  -说什么
- Nobody told you? - Tell me what?
我一直在单独监禁
I've been in solitary.
发生了什么
What happened?
杰森  还是没找到卢克
Jason, Luke is still missing.
什么
What?
不  这跟说好的不一样
No, that wasn't the deal.
-杰森  听我说  -不
- Jason, listen to me. - No.
我把关于麦克利什
I told the president everything about MacLeish,
卡特兰  还有蓝图的一切告诉了总统
Catalan, the blueprints.
你毋须保护任何东西了
There is nothing left for you to protect.
告诉我你对她了解多少
Tell me what you know about her.
杰森
Jason?
照片哪里来的
Where did you get that?
-我拍的  -还记得你留给我的线索吗
- I took it. - You gave me the lead, remember?
威德尔案  我知道他们带走了卢克
The Weddle case. I knew they had Luke.
我也知道了他们正是借此
I also knew this is how they got you
要挟你承认谋杀纳萨尔
to confess to Nassar's murder.
杰森  撤回你的证词
Jason, take your statement back.
把你知道的一切都告诉我
Tell me everything you know.
听着  如果他们知道了
Listen to me -- if they know
-我在和你合作...  -不会的
- that I'm cooperating with you... - They won't.
纳萨尔被关在最高设防的联邦监狱
They had Nassar in a federal maximum-security prison
他们却仍能杀了他
and still got to him.
他们已经暴露了  我们识穿了麦克利什
They're exposed now. We know about MacLeish.
-杰森  -汉娜
- Jason... - Hannah...
求求你  我们需要你的帮助
Please. We need your help.
如果你想帮我...
You want to help me...
就找回我儿子
find my son.
我只知道的是  根据白宫总机接线员的说法
All I know is what the White House switchboard operator told me
国会大厦的威胁评估报告
that Aaron made the call to the Secretary of Defense
被五角大楼撤回前
right before the threat-assessment memo
是亚伦给国防部长打了电话
was recalled by the Pentagon.
他与你对质了吗
And he confronted you?
是的  他知道了我在打听事情
Yes. He found out I was making inquiries.
他很生气  并且询问我在干什么
He was very upset. He asked what I was doing.
我告诉他  他得来问您
I told him he needed to talk to you.
好  很抱歉我将你置于如此境地
Okay, I'm -- I'm sorry I put you in this position,
之后的事就交给我吧
but I'll handle it from here.
确定不需要我跟进吗
Are you sure you don't want me to follow up?
-我可以...  -不用了  谢谢
- I can... - No, I've got it. Thank you.
艾米丽
Emily.
我们之间的谈话不能让别人知道  明白吗
I need you to keep this conversation between us. Understood?
-好的  -谢谢
- Of course. - Thank you.
总统先生  你不会真觉得他是叛徒吧
Sir, you don't really think he's a traitor, do you?
不
No.
不  我不这么觉得
No, I don't.
但在我有十足把握前
But until I can prove that definitively,
我得保持警惕  你也是
I have to keep my guard up, and so do you.
今时不同往日
We're living in a different world today than we were yesterday.
-怎么了  -霍斯拉滕议长来了  先生
- Yeah? - Speaker Hookstraten is here, sir.
好  让她进来吧
All right, send her in.
感谢你能在这么短的时间内与我会面
Thank you for seeing me on such short notice.
当然  议长女士
Yeah, of course, Madam Speaker.
正如之前所说  我只能给你几分钟的时间
Now, as I said before, I can only give you a few minutes.
半分钟就好  我要见总统先生
This will take 30 seconds. I need to see the president.
议长女士...
Ma'am --
如果并非要事  我也不会提出请求
I wouldn't be asking if it wasn't important.
我理解  但总统先生仍在康复中
I understand, but the president's still in recovery right now.
很显然  他仍在工作
Clearly, he's still conducting business.
对  但是...
Yes, but --
我需要与他会面
So... I need to see him.
不如告诉我是什么事
Why don't you tell me what it's regarding?
我会转告他的
And I'll relay it to him.
这完全是总统先生与我之间的事
What this is regarding is strictly between me and the president.
好吧
All right.
恕我直言  议长女士  我是总统的幕僚长
Respectfully, Madam Speaker, I-I'm his Chief of Staff.
了解事态是我的职责
It's my job to know what's going on.
可能是的  但我不会告诉你
Perhaps, but not from me.
他会知道是什么事的
He'll know what this is about.
如果他想  可以告诉你
He can tell you if he wants,
但我不会背叛他的信任
but I'm not gonna betray his confidence.
我会努力帮你安排
I'll try and schedule you in.
谢谢
Thank you.
务必尽力
Try hard.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
我能帮忙找到卢克·亚特伍德
I can help find Luke Atwood.
-让我联系州警  -别把这事私人化
- Let me liaise with state police -- - Don't make this personal.
这就是私事
It is personal.
我向杰森保证了会尽一切努力
I promised Jason I would do everything I can.
是的  那个男孩从被绑架开始
Yes, and the boy has been a state-wide
就已经成了全州范围内的首要任务
priority since he was taken.
你刚刚看到我又增派了三名探员
You just saw me put - three more agents on it myself.
他们中任何一个
Now, each one of them is more qualified
在失踪人口上都比你更有资历
in missing persons than you.
你现在的任务是为总统制定计划
Your job right now is to come up with a plan for the president.
你现在不能有个人感情
You can't afford to have feelings.
你自己也知道我说的是对的
I'm right. And you know it.
现在回去工作
Now let's get back to work.
总统先生  请容我再表达一遍
Mr. President, let me say again
贝丝和我知道你安然无恙有多么的高兴
how relieved Beth and I are to know you're okay.
那对我意义重大
That means a great deal.
你看到我早上的评论了吗
You catch my remarks this morning?
是的  我很欣赏  非常感谢
Yes, I did, and I - appreciated them. Thank you.
关于昨晚  你可能听说了
In regards to last night, you may have heard
有一些内部意见分歧
that there was some internal disagreement.
我下达了杀无赦的命令
I gave the shoot-to-kill order
因为我不想看到更多无辜的人受到伤害
'cause I didn't want to see more innocent people get hurt.
所有情报都显示此人是专业杀手
All the intel suggested this guy was a pro,
他也不会接受被活捉
he wasn't gonna be taken alive.
我理解
I understand.
我可能处理方式不同
I might have handled it differently.
但是如果说成为总统之后
But if there's one thing that I've learned
我学到了什么
since becoming president,
那就是做在极大的压力下生死抉择
it's how difficult it is
有多么的艰难
to make life-and-death decisions under extreme pressure.
谢谢  总统先生
Thank you, sir.
我仅承担了这份工作一天
You know, I only held the job for a day,
就已经让我感激
but it did make me appreciate
你为国家所做的一切了
everything you've done for this country.
他说了什么
And then what did he say?
他向我表示感谢
He thanked me.
然后告诉我他希望我接手
Then he told me he wants me to take over
他本月余下的公开日程
his public schedule for the rest of the month,
直到他完全康复
till he's back at full strength.
那太好了
Ah, that's excellent.
-那就是你要做的  -是的
- That's what you'll do. - Yeah.
与此同时  我们静待进一步指示
And for the moment, we lay low until further instruction.
哪种指示
What kind of instructions?
另一次刺杀
Another attempt?
我很怀疑
I doubt it.
我想在短期内我们会巩固现有成果
I think we consolidate our gains in the short term.
贝丝  还有太多未了结的事
Beth, there are so many loose ends.
有人去处理未了结的事了  彼得
And the loose ends are being attended to, Peter.
卡特兰已经死了  威尔士探员被监禁
Catalan is dead. Agent Wells is in custody.
她会被解决掉的
She'll be taken care of.
我们会平安度过
We'll get through this.
一向如此
We always do.
我从没有这么生气过
I've never felt anger like this before.
我这辈子还从没打过人
You know, I've never even hit someone in my entire life,
上小学时都没有
not even in grade school.
我总是那个和事佬
I was always the peacemaker.
但我看到他时  他就站在那儿笑着
But when I saw him... just standing there, smiling,
我就想伸手掐死他
I wanted to reach out and strangle him.
说实话  我觉得我本可能杀了他
Honestly, I think I could have killed him.
你藏得很好  先生
You hid it well, sir.
他以为他是在耍你  但事实上
He thinks he's playing you, but in reality,
他在大家眼中
he's a prisoner in plain sight,
在美国公众一致认为的囚犯了
in full view of the American public,
更别提还有一群特工处的特工
not to mention a phalanx of Secret Service agents.
我们只要耐心等待
We just got to be patient.
他就会出纰漏  放松警惕
He'll make a mistake, lower his guard.
到那时...
And when he does...
他就任我处置了
He's mine.
您感觉怎么样  总统先生
How are you feeling, Mr. President?
好多了  谢谢
Much better. Thank you.
好吧  你想从哪儿开始
All right. Where would you like to start?
我先说
Let me begin.
我知道你跟艾米丽关系紧张
I understand there's some tension between you and Emily.
她一直在查我的通话记录
She's been looking into my phone records.
是我让她查的
At my direction.
我也要求她不要让你知道
I also asked her to keep you out of the loop.
我能问为什么吗
May I ask why?
当然  我该给你个解释
Of course. You... You deserve an explanation.
你可是我的参谋长
You're my Chief of Staff.
事实是  在特工处的要求下
The truth is, at the request of the Secret Service,
我不得不重新审查我的整个核心交际圈
I have had to re-vet my entire inner circle.
因为那场爆炸
Because of the bombing,
当晚有上千人丧生
a thousand people died that night, and...
而且事件疑云重重
and it left more questions than answers.
-希望你能理解  -当然  先生
- I hope you understand. - Yeah. Of course, sir.
我让艾米丽负责你的背景调查
I asked Emily to coordinate your background check.
所以她自然不能泄露这件事
So naturally, she couldn't divulge what she was doing
因为这是机密
because it was classified.
明白
Understood.
抱歉给你带来了困扰
And I apologize for any confusion,
但责任在我  不在艾米丽
but it was my call, not Emily's.
总统先生  您没必要道歉
Mr. President, there's no need for apologies.
这一切都说得通了
It all makes perfect sense now.
好  很好  你有什么消息
Okay. Great. What have you got?
霍斯拉滕议长来见我了
Speaker Hookstraten came to see me,
她说她要跟你谈谈
and she said she needed to talk to you,
她说你知道是什么事
and you would know what it's about.
有隐情
Something's here.
我们穷追不舍  他定会露出马脚
We shake this tree hard enough, it'll fall out.
你怎么这么肯定
How can you be so sure?
麦克利什部队的八名幸存者
The eight surviving members of MacLeish's army unit
十年来一直在说谎
have all been lying for a decade.
他们之间肯定有突破口
There's got to be a weak link in here somewhere,
肯定有人有个人问题  吸毒  酗酒之类的
someone with personal problems, drugs, booze, something.
所以你是怎么想的
So what are you thinking?
我们找出那个人并从他突破  但要小心
We find that person... and break him, but carefully.
我们不能让让麦克利什察觉
We can't afford to tip MacLeish off.
我们只是想引蛇出洞  而不是打草惊蛇
We need to rattle his cage, not shatter it.
好
Right.
不要  救命
No! Help!
不
No!
我很抱歉  我不是故意要吓你们
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
-你还好吗  爸爸  -我还好
- Are you okay, Daddy? - Yeah.
我只是...
I just, uh...
做了个噩梦
I had a bad dream.
你手上的是什么
What do you got there?
我为你画了幅画
I drew it for you.
为了我
For me?
真好看
It's beautiful.
你是从博物馆偷来的吗
Did you steal it from a museum?
不  是我画的
No. I drew it.
-爸爸刚才大叫了一声  -他没有
- Daddy screamed. - He did not.
最新海外影视剧下载
你站在这里多久了
How -- how long have you been standing there?
一直等到欣赏完你的美妙琴声
Long enough to hear how good you are.
我都不知道你弹得这么好
I didn't even know you played.
我曾经很认真地练过一段时间
I was serious about it for a while,
但现在只当是一种放松方式
but now I just play to release stress.
有效果吗
And does it work?
偶尔有
Sometimes.
我刚从医院回来
So, I just got back from the hospital.
我知道你为什么这么谨慎
Listen, I-I get why you're being so cagey.
事关国家机密
It was a matter of national security.
亚伦  他让我审查你
Aaron, he asked me to vet you.
此事需严格保密  所以你问我的时候
It was strictly classified, so when you confronted me,
我不能向你说出详情
I couldn't tell you what was going on.
我理解  他告诉我了
I know. No, he told me.
我...
I'm...
很抱歉  我之前有点不理智
I'm sorry. I-I was a bit of a jerk.
我懂的  这对于我们俩都很有压力
I get it. It was stressful for both of us.
是的
Yeah.
你还有什么事吗
So, you, uh -- you take any requests?
我要回去了
I should get back.
好的
Yeah.
好的  我也是
Yeah, me too.
再见
See you around.
Yeah.
摩托车维修中心
XL1200C型赛车
XL1200C Sportster.
真是辆好车
That's a nice ride.
修好后我可以给你开一个好价钱
Yeah. I can get you a good price on her once I'm through.
我觉得这车对我来说有点大
I think it's a little bit too much bike for me.
-阿尔文·乔纳  -是的
- Alvin Joyner? - Yeah.
联调局探员  约翰逊
Special Agent Johnson, FBI.
我几周前和联调局的人
I already talked to the FBI, weeks ago,
谈过麦克利什队长的事了
about Captain MacLeish.
只是个例行的背景后续调查而已  阿尔文
Oh, it's just a routine follow-up on our background check, Alvin.
局里不希望出任何差错
The Bureau doesn't like to get anything wrong,
尤其是涉及到
especially when it involves
美国副总统时
the vice president of the United States.
我在文件正式归档之前
But I need to cross a few T's and dot a few I's
需要确认一些信息
before we can officially close the file.
-可以吗  -当然没问题  问吧
- Is that okay? - Yeah, sure. Shoot.
在2005年11月14日
About this mission to Kunar Province,
库纳尔省的行动中
November 14, 2005,
你的事后报告说你是和20个人一起出发的
your after-action report says you set out with 20 men.
这属实吗
Is that correct?
是的  三支中队
Yeah. Three squads.
但是我们并非满员状态
But we weren't full strength.
莫罗膝盖受伤
Morrow had a bad knee,
罗德里格斯当时在休探亲假
and Rodriguez was on family leave.
好吧  那为什么出勤直升机的乘客名单上
Okay, uh, so, why does the outbound-helicopter manifest
写的是21名军人呢
say 21 troops?
不知道
I don't know.
可能有人弄错了
Maybe somebody made a mistake.
我一开始也这么认为
You know, I thought that,
我就去问了相关技术军官
so I asked the warrant officer involved,
他说绝对没有弄错
and he said absolutely not.
他说他们绝对不会犯这样的错误
He said they can't afford to make mistakes like that.
这可是性命攸关的事
Lives depend on it.
那我就不知道该跟你说什么好了
I don't know what to tell you.
有没有可能那天有其他人
Is it possible someone else
跟你们一起行动了呢  阿尔文
joined your mission that night, Alvin?
-不  不可能  -你确定
- No. No. No way. - You sure?
因为技术军官说了
Because the warrant officer said that
有时候会派外部人员参与任务
sometimes outside personnel will be assigned to missions --
情报员  中情局特工之类的
intelligence officers, CIA, stuff like that.
不  从没有过
Nope. Never happened.
好吧
All right.
看来我们该说的都说完了
Well, I guess we're done here then.
-祝你好运  -谢谢配合
- Good luck. - Thanks for your time.
去告知总统  有好戏上演了
Tell the president it's game on.
他会去找麦克利什
He's gonna run to MacLeish.
总统先生  我理解您身负重担
Mr. President, I appreciate that you have a job to do,
但放任您在术后如此短的时间内回去工作
but I wouldn't be doing mine if I didn't advise you
而我未加劝阻的话  就是我工作的失职
against leaving the hospital so soon after surgery.
上校  我非常理解你
Captain, I understand completely.
但是我真的需要回去
But I really do have to get back.
事关国家安全
It's a matter of national security.
而且是你说的
And you were the one who said
你为我的康复速度感到高兴
you were really happy with my progress.
是的  但我也告诫过您不可操劳过度
True, but I also cautioned against undue stress.
那我恐怕是入错行了
Well, I'm afraid I've got the wrong job for that.
你看  你根本拗不过他
See? You're not gonna win with him.
-我也发现了  -我向你保证
- So I'm discovering. - Look, I promise you,
我会尽量多休息
I will do everything I can to take it easy.
而且上次我查了一下  我的军衔比你高
Besides, last time I checked, I think I outrank you.
艾丽克斯  我知道你生我的气了
Alex, I know you're mad at me,
但我真的需要回去工作
but I really do need to get back.
你一定要相信我
You're gonna have to trust me.
汤姆  我注意到你看发布会时的表情了
Tom, I saw the way you looked watching that press conference.
发生什么事了  与麦克利什有关吗
What is going on? Is it MacLeish?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
我能应付得来
I can handle it.
艾丽克斯  你没明白我的意思
Alex, you're not hearing me.
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
你是想说  身为总统  你不能告诉我吧
You mean the president can't tell me.
现在  我们不分彼此
Right now, we're one in the same.
我们刚从诺福克回来
Yeah, we're just coming back from Norfolk now.
还行吧
Oh, it was fine.
不停地握手
Shook a lot of hands,
在驱逐舰的舰首上开了瓶香槟
broke a champagne bottle on a destroyer's bow.
都是些例行公事
It was strictly routine.
我也爱你
Yeah, I love you, too.
美国邮政管理局
我看见你留下的粉笔标志了  怎么了
I saw your chalk mark. What's up?
是乔纳  他想见你
It's Joyner. He wants to see you.
为什么
Why?
联调局今天来找他了
The FBI came to see him today.
又来  为了什么事
Again? What about?
说是例行后续调查
Said it was a routine follow-up,
和库纳尔任务的直升机乘客名单有关
something to do with a helicopter manifest on the Kunar mission.
直升机乘客名单
Helicopter manifest?
没错  我觉得只是些官僚工作
Yeah. It sounds like bureaucratic busywork to me.
这不就完了吗
Well, it sounds like the end of it then.
对啊  但乔纳不这么想  你了解他的  队长
Yeah, except for Joyner. You know Alvin, Cap.
他比我们其余的人都要严重
He took it harder than the rest of us.
他一直进出康复中心
He's been in and out of rehab.
不必费多大力气就能逼死他了
Wouldn't take much to push him over the edge.
我也不想这样为难你
I hate to put you in this position,
但是他不肯听我的  他坚持要...
but he wouldn't listen to me, insisted that he had to --
不不不  我当然会见他
No. No, no, no, no, no. Of course I'll see him.
对不起  队长
I'm sorry, Captain.
没事
It's okay.
即兴发挥  适时改编  完胜全场
Improvise, adapt, overcome, right?
告诉他  我...
Tell him I'll, uh... yeah.
我会在上次那个地方等他
I'll meet him at the, uh, same place as last time,
今晚九点
tonight, 21:00.
收到
Roger that.
好
Okay.
我和总统说了你想见他
I told the president you wanted to see him.
-然后呢  -他说能见你时  自然会找你
- And? - And he said he'd get back to you when he can.
这样不够
Not good enough.
总统改变了计划  议长女士
The president just changed his plans, ma'am.
他今晚就要出院
He's getting out of the hospital tonight.
-今晚  为什么  -因为他想回来工作
- Tonight? Why? - Because he wants to get back to work.
如果你想和他说的事十万火急的话
Now, listen, if what you want to share with him
那你就告诉我吧
is time-sensitive, just tell me.
事关那位枪手
It's about the gunman.
与他有何相关
What about the gunman?
我想知道为什么联调局
I want to know why the FBI
一枪崩了我们的李·哈维·奥斯瓦尔德
blew away our own Lee Harvey Oswald.
被认为是肯尼迪总统遇刺案的主凶
疑犯对执法机关构成了直接威胁
The suspect posed an immediate threat to law enforcement.
少来这套
Oh, come on.
这是一系列空前巨大的阴谋
It was a cluster of epic proportions.
枪手是独行侠  还是某组织的成员
Was the shooter a lone wolf, part of a group?
我们永远不得而知了
We'll never know now.
但是今早麦克利什副总统
But there was Vice President MacLeish this morning
却视之为一场胜仗
turning it into a victory lap.
-为什么  -你当时不在场  议长女士
- Why? - You weren't in the room, ma'am.
但是你在  亚伦  到底怎么回事
But you were, Aaron. What happened?
麦克利什是否参与其中
Was MacLeish involved -- yes or no?
就连总统都怀疑麦克利什
Even the President has his suspicions about MacLeish.
他亲口告诉我的
He told me so himself.
还是他没告诉你
Or didn't he fill you in?
你...  你在说什么
What -- What are you talking about?
他当然告诉我了
Of course he told me.
那你也该知道他让我盯紧麦克利什
Well, then you know that he asked me to keep an eye on MacLeish.
我需要知道详情  亚伦
I need to be in the loop, Aaron.
抱歉  我不能...
I'm sorry. I can't --
如果白宫不配合
If the White House doesn't cooperate,
我将召开国会听证会
I'll just call a congressional hearing...
或是记者招待会
or maybe a press conference.
你不能公开这件事
You can't go public with this.
你在保护什么
What are you trying to protect?
还是该问  你在保护谁
Or should I say who are you trying to protect?
毕竟你是那个把麦克利什推上副总统之位的人
After all, it was you who pushed MacLeish for V.P.
比其他人都积极
more than anyone else.
这样说太偏颇了
Now -- Now, that's low.
但是事实  昨晚发生什么了
But accurate. What happened last night?
好吧
Fine.
那我们就在委员会上见了
I'll see you in committee.
我们逮到了一个枪手
We had the shooter contained.
联调局准备活捉
FBI was ready to apprehend,
但被麦克利什驳回了
but MacLeish overruled them.
为什么
Why?
他说他想要保护出勤特工的生命安全
He said he wanted to protect the lives of the men on the ground.
我告诉他总统更希望生擒抢手
I told him the president would want to take him alive,
但他还是下令了
but he -- he gave the order anyway.
什么命令
What order?
就地射杀
Shoot to kill.
此事不能外泄  好吗
And that's for your ears only, all right?
当然
Of course.
我们先开始限制他对国家安全文件
We start by limiting his access
和情报简报的读取权限
to national-security documents and intelligence briefings.
我们会用全体工作人员安全审查做幌子
We do it under the guise of a staff-wide security review.
亚伦不会知道此事只针对他一人
Aaron won't know he's being targeted.
好的  我希望保持他的不知情
Okay, good. I want to keep it that way.
我还建议更新他的最高级别敏感信息权限
I also recommend we renew his TS/SCI clearance.
这样就可以获取他的经济状况
That'll give us access to his finances,
近期旅行记录和个人通讯信息
recent travel, personal contacts.
好的  要记住
Okay, just remember --
我们是想洗清他的嫌疑  而非毁了他
we want to clear him, not bury him.
当然  长官
Affirmative, sir.
麦克利什那边怎么样了
Where does that put us with MacLeish?
已经设好陷阱了
Trap has been set.
威尔士探员在监视麦克利什的一个老战友
Agent Wells is sitting on one of MacLeish's old Army buddies,
就等着他采取行动了
just waiting for him to make a move.
同时  我通知了他的安保人员
In the meantime, I've filled in his security detail,
告诉他们按副总统要求
told them to give the vice president
给他足够的空间
a wide berth, should he request it.
接下来唯一能做的就是等待了
I guess the only thing left to do is wait.
这总是最艰难的部分  总统先生
It's always the hardest part, sir.
是的
Yeah.
你在开玩笑吧
You can't be serious.
我告诉过你  我们现在走每一步都要小心翼翼
I told you every move we make now has to be cautious.
如此暴露自己过于危险
Exposing yourself like this. It's too risky.
我们以前也和乔纳经历着类似的事
We've been down this road with Joyner before.
-这不...  -这不值得  彼得
- It's not... - It's not worth it, Peter.
总统之位唾手可得
You're a heartbeat away from the presidency.
让别人来善后吧
Let someone else fix the problem.
我是他唯一能够倾诉的人
I'm the only one he'll talk to.
我不是这个意思
That's not what I mean.
-不  -如果他像你说得那样痛苦
- No. - If he's in as much pain as you say,
我们这是在帮他的忙
we'll be doing him a favor.
-不  -你不再是军人了  彼得
- No. - You're not in the army anymore, Peter.
我们已宣誓要为更伟大的事业而奋斗
We pledged ourselves to a higher cause.
贝丝  他是我的手下
Beth, he's one of my men.
我们一起经历过地狱般的折磨
We've been through hell together.
而现在他是战争牺牲品
And now he becomes another casualty of war.
战争的牺牲品
A casualty of war?
-你听到自己在说什么了吗  -你有吗
- Are you hearing yourself? - Are you?
联调局找上他了
The FBI came to see him.
只是个例行的后续调查
On a routine follow-up.
他只是需要打消自己的顾虑
The guy just needs some reassurance.
我能安抚好他
I can give it to him.
好吧
Fine.
去和他谈谈  仅此一次
Talk to him this once.
但如果没用的话
But if it doesn't work,
他就需要消失了
the problem has to be eliminated.
没有牺牲就没有胜利  记得吗
No victory without sacrifice, remember?
我记得
I remember.
亚特伍德
Atwood.
我和你没什么好说的
I got nothing to say to you.
杰森  事关卢克
Jason, it's about Luke.
杰森
Jason.
等一下
Wait.
-先生  -先生
- Sir. - Sir!
不  让他过去  让他过去
No! Let him go! Let him...
车备好了  副总统先生
Car's ready, Mr. Vice President.
谢谢你  里奇
Thanks, Rich.
只有你们两个  是吗
It's just the two of you, right?
正如您的要求  先生
As you requested, sir.
我马上下去
I'll be right down.
你还好吗
You okay?
你有什么喝的吗
You got anything to drink?
心情这么"好"啊
That good, huh?
喝吧
Go ahead.
我是说...  好吧
I mean, that -- Okay.
这是瓶麦卡伦18年威士忌  你自便吧
That's an 18-year Macallan, but, yeah, help yourself.
谢谢
Thank you.
是因为亚伦吗
Is this about Aaron?
我押20块事关"政治问题"
Okay. I'll take - "political malaise" for $20.
-还真说中了  -谢谢
- Oh, you suck. - Thank you.
我原以为自己知道这里是如何运转的
I thought I knew how this town worked,
但现在我也弄不懂了
but it doesn't make sense anymore.
每一个我以为能够信赖的人
You know, every-- everyone I thought I could count on,
每件事  都无关紧要了
everything -- it doesn't matter.
最终都是体制获胜  不是吗
The system wins in the end, right?
我也不知道  也许我错了
I don't know. Maybe I'm wrong.
也许我太天真了  也许二者都是
Maybe I'm naive. Maybe I'm both.
谁知道呢
Who knows?
我告诉过你我在白宫的第一份工作
Did I ever tell you about how I got
是怎么得来的吗
my first job at the White House?
《哈佛讽刺文社》
Harvard Lampoon connection.
我告诉过你吗
I told you?
赛斯  每次私下和你聊天
Seth, nobody can have a personal conversation
你都会提到哈佛
with you without Harvard coming up,
通常30秒内就会说到
usually within the first 30 seconds.
并不是这样的  我是在剑桥上的学
That's not true. I always say I went to school in Cambridge.
不管怎样  翻篇吧
Anyway, I'm ignoring that.
我的意思是  当我刚来这的时候
My point is that - when I first started here,
我只是底层员工  对吗
I mean, I was floored, all right?
我走路不超过15米就得停下
I couldn't walk more than 50 feet without stopping.
现在我在这里  在白宫
Here I was - at the White House, right?
第二代移民
The son of immigrants.
-我无法相信...  -等一下
- I mean, I couldn't believe -- - Wait. Hold on.
-我以为你父亲是一名成功的工程师  -别打岔
- I thought your dad's a successful engineer. - Don't interrupt.
我的意思是我无法相信我能走到这步
What I'm saying was that I couldn't believe that I was here.
然后工作上的烦心事就上来了
And then work took over,
现实开始展现出它丑陋的一面
and reality reared its ugly head.
我才开始意识到为什么华盛顿是这样
And I started to realize why Washington is the way it is.
后来在国会大厦被袭击后
And then I bump into Tom Kirkman in the bathroom
我在厕所遇到了汤姆·柯克曼
after the entire government's been blown up,
而他身上只有正直感与慈悲心
and he's nothing but decency and compassion.
他为国效力的愿望远远大于自己的野心
I mean, this guy is service over ambition,
大公无私
integrity above expedience.
于是这让我感觉到
And it reminded me what it felt like
我们不应该只为自己着想
to be part of something bigger than yourself...
而是要为我们心目中向往的美国
what it felt like to be part of the kind of America
做出自己的贡献
that you want to believe in.
我今晚仍然是这么想的
I still feel that way tonight.
我又何尝不是呢
So how come I don't?
你是完美主义者
'Cause you're a perfectionist.
可突然间一切都不那么完美了
And suddenly things don't seem so perfect.
我又不是孩子了  赛斯
No. I'm not a child, Seth.
我知道这世界并不完美
I know things aren't perfect.
是的  但你觉得自己可以让这个世界变得美好
Yes, but you think you can make things perfect.
这个...
Well...
也不是...  可能吧
It's not that I... Maybe.
只是可能吗
Maybe.
艾米丽  你工作非常尽责
Emily, come on. You're doing a great job.
即使完美主义者也并非一帆风顺
Even perfectionists have their ups and downs.
别怪我说得简单  我觉得你只是难过
Not to oversimplify it, but I think you're probably sad.
我们都很难过
We're all really sad.
这并没有错
There's nothing wrong with that.
你应该回家  安全地回家
You need to go home, get home safely,
好好睡一觉
get a really good night's sleep.
我现在只有这些建议
That is all of my advice at this hour.
明天还会有更多
You get more tomorrow.
-谢谢  -不不不
- Thank you. - No, no, no.
-闭嘴吧  晚安  -晚安
- Shut up. Good night. - Good night.
-有什么能帮你的吗  女士  -是的
- Yes, ma'am, can I help you? - I hope so.
我叫安吉拉·琳赛
My name is Angela Lindsay.
我是佩顿-斯坦-戈塞特律师行的律师
I'm an attorney with Payton, Stein, and Gossett.
你们拘留了一名联调局探员  汉娜·威尔士
You have an FBI agent in custody -- Hannah Wells.
她的家人雇了我们
We've been retained by her family.
我需要马上见到她
I need to see her immediately, please.
新信息
未知号码
威尔士被释放  下落不明
-什么事  -我是贝丝
- Yeah. - It's Beth.
你不应该给我打电话
You shouldn't be calling me.
盘问乔纳的联调局探员是谁
The FBI agent who questioned Joyner -- who was it?
我不知道  乔纳没说
I don't know. Joyner didn't say.
男的还是女的
Well, was it a man or a woman?
女的  亚洲人  他好像说过  怎么了
A woman, Asian woman, I think he said. Why?
快点  彼得  接电话
Come on, Peter. Pick up.
-您所拨打的用户...  -该死
- The subscriber you are trying to reach... - Damn it.
保持安静
阿尔文  这两位是达姆沙克和帕尔默探员
Alvin, these are Agents Damashek and Palmer.
请抬起胳膊  先生
Hold your arms out, please, sir.
谢谢你们  我一会就回去
Thanks, gentleman. Be with you in a few minutes.
我们走走
Let's take a walk.
对...  对不起  队长
I'm -- I'm sorry, Cap.
不不不  不用道歉
No, no, no, don't be sorry.
怎么了
What's going on?
我太紧张了
I get nervous, you know?
会被人发现的
Someone's gonna find out.
联调局手上有乘客名单
The FBI -- they got this manifest.
都是些形式主义的文件
It's paperwork, red tape.
你知道军方的
You know the army.
我知道  队长  但事实是
I know, Cap, but the truth --
事实很久之前就被掩盖了  阿尔文
The truth got buried a long time ago, Alvin.
但于我  于我的良心都没有
Not for me, not in here.
我还是会看到他们的脸  我们做过的事
I still see all their faces, what we did.
你得振作起来  伙计
You got to pull yourself together, man.
我希望我死在那里  队长
I wish I'd died there, Captain.
-别这样  -我发誓
- Oh, come on. - I swear.
我希望自己没能回来
I wish I never came back.
那天的事不是你的错
What happened that day was not your fault.
我们被出卖了  记得吗
We were betrayed, remember?
我们必须自卫
We had to defend ourselves.
为了拯救彼此我们不得不那样做
We did what we had to do to save each other.
鉴于我的副总统身份
This new office I'm in, I mean,
我不能再这样来这里了
I can't be making visits like this anymore,
所以我要知道  我能信任你吗
so I need to know... can I count on you?
《约翰福音》第八章第32节
John 8:32.
阿尔文  不  阿尔文
Alvin, no. Alvin.
"你们必晓得真理"
"And you will know the truth."
这很重要  这真的很重要
This is important. This is so important.
-"真理必叫你们得以自由"  -你不懂多重要
- "And the truth will set you free." - You don't know
这是圣经  不是政府
how important. That's the Bible. It's not the government.
政府对真理没有兴趣
The government's not interested in truth.
政府才是撒谎的人
It's the government that lies.
他们把我们送进屠杀场
They sent us into a slaughterhouse,
然后掩盖了事实
and then they covered it up.
他们利用我们  那我们就利用他们
They used us, so we used them.
是  你说了谎  我们都说了谎  阿尔文
Yes, you lied. We all did, Alvin.
我对国会说谎  为了保护部队  保护你
I lied to Congress to protect the unit, to protect you.
你要对得起...
You got to live up to your end...
-够了  上吧  -我这样做并保护我们
- That's it. Go. - of the bargain and protect us.
因为如果你失败了
'Cause if you fail to do that,
你不仅会毁掉我们
you're not only gonna destroy us --
联调局  不许动
FBI! Freeze! Don't move!
麦克利什副总统  我以对美国国会
Vice President MacLeish, I'm arresting you for perjury
作伪证罪逮捕你
in front of the United States Congress.
把手放在头上
Put your hands on your head.
-现在  -快跑  队长
- Now. - Run, Cap!
快点  目标在180米外
Let's go. Target is 200 yards out.
下一发会打中的
The next one counts.
你不会对我开枪的
You're not gonna shoot me.
把手放在头上
Put your hands on your head.
你什么证据都没有  威尔士
You got nothing, Wells.
跪下
On your knees.
我是美国副总统
I'm the vice president of the United States.
你只是个警察
You're just a cop.
不
No!
谢谢
Thank you.
别操劳过度了
Don't work too hard.
谢谢
Thank you.
再见
Take care.
白宫安全网络访问
拒绝访问
我们车上见吧
Perhaps I'll meet you at the car.